draftday.com 2019-01-17

# Privacy Policy, Frequently Asked Questions

Last update posted: April 21, 2016

DraftDay.com (“DraftDay”) recognizes that people who use DraftDay value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected via the DraftDay.com website and mobile app (the “Service”). DraftDay provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using DraftDay.

Your use of DraftDay and any personal information you provide through the Service remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service (https://www.draftday.com/tos), as each may be updated from time to time.

Last update posted: April 21, 2016

Please note that any video, image, or other content you post on DraftDay.com (e.g., your name with a comment to a blog post) is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy and may be published by DraftDay.

Any questions, comments or complaints that you might have should be forwarded in writing to:

DraftDay Gaming Group, Inc.

902 Broadway, 11th Floor

New York, NY 10010

**Information We Collect**

1\. User Provided Information: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name, email address, PayPal or credit card billing information, contacts you choose to submit, and profile photo) to DraftDay when choosing to participate in various activities on the Service such as registering for an account, participating in contests, uploading pictures, posting messages, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists.

2\. Cookies Information: When you visit the DraftDay.com website, we may send one or more cookies - small files - to your computer or other device, which may enable us or others to uniquely identify your browser. DraftDay uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Session cookies are temporary and typically disappear after you close your browser. You may be able to reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the DraftDay.com website may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.'

3\. Log File Information: When you use DraftDay, our servers may automatically record certain information that your device sends whenever you visit any website and use certain apps. These server logs may include information such as your web or app request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

4\. Clear GIFs Information: When you use DraftDay, we may employ technology such as "clear GIFs" (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users. In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by specific users.

5. Additional Mobile App Information: When you use our mobile app, we also may collect mobile device information like operating system and hardware type, numbers or codes that are unique to your particular device, device state information, default device language, the location of your device, and app usage information.

6. Location Data Information: Certain services including GeoComply, will make use of your location data. If you use such services, you consent to us transmitting, collecting, maintaining, processing and using your location data in order to provide and improve location-based services. You may withdraw this consent at any time by turning off the location settings or by notifying us in writing that you would like to withdraw such consent.

**The Way DraftDay Uses This Information**

1\. We use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of DraftDay, including but not limited to the following: (a) providing you our products and services, including our games; (b) processing and responding to inquiries; (c) alerting you to new Service features, special events, products and services, or certain third-party products or services in which we think you will be interested; and (d) enforcing the legal terms that govern your use of the Service.

2\. We may use your information to contact you for both marketing and non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major DraftDay changes or for customer service purposes).

3\. We use your information to improve the quality and design of DraftDay and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services, such as by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.

4\. We also use cookies, clear gifs, log file information and mobile app information for purposes such as (a) remembering information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit DraftDay; (b) providing custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitoring the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitoring aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) tracking your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

5\. We may anonymize or aggregate your information for business purposes, including for reporting and research. Anonymous and/or aggregated data does not identify you, and we may use and disclose such information without limitation.

**When DraftDay Discloses Information**

Our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, agents, or other businesses or persons may have authorized access to your information (such as name or email address) for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf, including by using the information to make improvements to the services they provide. We may share your personally identifiable information third parties for their commercial or marketing use with your consent or as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to your requests for customer service. As agreed in our Terms of Service, we may use personal information about you (such as your name and photo) in connection with marketing and publicity purposes. We will publish a profile page that includes your username, the date you became a member, your stats from previous contests and, if you uploaded one, your profile picture. When you participate in a contest, we may publish your username on a list of the contest participants, along with a link to your profile page. We also may share personally identifiable information in other situations with your consent.

DraftDay also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information that DraftDay believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Service, take precautions against liability or harm, to investigate and respond to third-party claims or allegations, to respond to a subpoena, legal order, or official request, to protect the security or integrity of our Service, and to protect the rights, property, or safety of DraftDay, our Users or others. Information also may be shared as described in the Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy section below.

**Your Choices**

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through DraftDay, in which case DraftDay may not be able to provide certain services to you.

To protect your privacy and security, we reserve the right to take reasonable steps (such as requesting your password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and account information at all times.

Please contact DraftDay with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices by using the contact us form.

**Data Security**

DraftDay uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to DraftDay and you do so at your own risk.

**Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy  
**

In the event that DraftDay is involved in a merger, acquisition, sale, bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, or other change of control, there may be a disclosure of your personally identifiable information to another entity related to such event, and we may not control how the information is treated, transferred, or used by that entity.

**Third Party Advertising and Analytics Companies**

Certain ads appearing on DraftDay are delivered to Members/Groups by our advertising partners. Our advertising partners may use cookies and other automated technologies to collect data, including the technologies described in the “Information We Collect” section above. Doing this allows the ad companies to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, the ad companies may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and measure your interaction with each ad. This information allows ad companies to deliver targeted advertisements that may be of increased interest to you, both on our Service and elsewhere online. Note that we also work with third-party analytics companies to collect data on our Service through cookies and other automated means. In some cases, the third parties mentioned in this section may maintain the information they collect in personally identifiable form.

**Publicity**

Except where prohibited, participation in a contest constitutes the player's consent to the use by DraftDay and its agents of player's name, likeness, voice, opinions, and biographical information for publicity, advertising, trade, or promotional purposes in any media or manner, now known or hereafter devised, worldwide, without further payment, consideration, notice, or approval, as described in more detail in our Terms of Service.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

If you reside in California, you may request certain general information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the following address:

DraftDay Gaming Group, Inc.

902 Broadway, 11th Floor

New York, NY 10010

**Changes and updates**

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "Last update posted" date above. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of DraftDay constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.
